<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anthonys Digital Garden</title>
    <link>https://sonofzappa.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anthonys Digital Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 09:01:54 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sonofzappa.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://sonofzappa.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 09:01:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sonofzappa.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the jungle!</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the jungle!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://sonofzappa.github.io/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sonofzappa.github.io/now/</guid>
      <description>This about page is an idea from Derek Sivers, it tells you what I am working on right now:
2021-12-26 From Illinois
Enjoying and working on my new old house Last spring we moved to a cozy little house far outside of the city. As the weather cools I am working on more and more inside the house. The small neighborhood vibe and Christmas lights, my first fireplace all make the winter more pleasant.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;This about page is an idea from &lt;a href=&#34;https://nownownow.com/about&#34;&gt;Derek Sivers&lt;/a&gt;, it tells you what I am working on right now:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2021-12-26 From Illinois&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;enjoying-and-working-on-my-new-old-house&#34;&gt;Enjoying and working on my new old house&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last spring we moved to a cozy little house far outside of the city. As the weather cools I am working on more and more inside the house. The small neighborhood vibe and Christmas lights, my first fireplace all make the winter more pleasant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;celebrating-the-holidays-with-friends-and-family&#34;&gt;Celebrating the holidays with friends and family&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After last years pause on parties, I was grateful to be able to see my family for the holidays again this year. I recently went to the Art Institute with friends I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen for a while. This was probably the longest stretch of not visiting the Art Institute as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;reflecting-on-the-year-and-planning-next&#34;&gt;Reflecting on the year and planning next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the time of year, I start to review what I have done this year and what I had hoped to have done. This year already looks like a win in many catagories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;writing&#34;&gt;Writing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Setting up this new site on &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;. I chose Hugo for it&amp;rsquo;s speed and the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s open source. After a break, I am back to writing about things that interest me and take me down rabit holes. This is where I will post them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;planning-garden-for-next-spring&#34;&gt;Planning garden for next spring&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of work to be done before anything can be planted. The goal is to balance productive fertility and an aesthetically pleasing retreat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;rehabbing-knee-pain-from-running&#34;&gt;Rehabbing knee pain from running&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started running a couple years ago and finally got the hang of it this summer. Then I went to far and got an overuse injury. Trying to rehab it myself with information from others, books and youtube.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*About Now Pages&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
